Guide to the Herbert C. (Herbert Coffin) Jones Papers, 1903-1954
Department of Special Collections
- LEGISLATIVE SESSION, 1931(Legislative Correspondence, filed according to Subject Letter.
  - Building and Loan Act of 1931 (Box 59, Folder 462)
  - Building and Loan (Box 59, Folder 463)
  - Building and Loan, Bank Tax Report, 1931,Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 464)
  - C (Box 59, Folder 465)
  - Chain Stores, 1930-31
  - Civil Service, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 466)
  - Colleges, Proposed State College at Sacramento, 1931
  - County Government
  - D (Box 60, Folder 467)
  - Dried Fruit (Measure introduced by Senator Jones)
  - E (Box 60, Folder 468)
  - Education, Legislation on, 1931
  - Education, Correspondence, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 469)
  - F (Box 60, Folder 470)
  - Fish and Game
  - G (Box 60, Folder 471)
  - Gasoline Tax. Report of Research Department and Recommendations of California Farm Bureau (SB 443, AB 972), 1931
  - HI (Box 61, Folder 472)
  - Industrial Accident Commission. (Bills, Mr. Burke, 552-558) (Box 61, Folder 473)
  - Investment Trusts, 1931
  - Insurance. in re: qualification of Insurance Agents, 1931
  - J (Box 61, Folder 474)
  - Judges, Salaries
  - KL
  - M (Box 61, Folder 475)
  - Majority, Age of (399)
  - Map Act (subdivision) in re: County Planning, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 476)
  - Married Women (AB 1630) employment of married women in public schools
  - Medicine (SB175) (Box 61, Folder 477)
  - Milk (bill, 1927)
  - Motor Vehicle License Plate
  - Music Teachers
  - Modern Tendencies in Legislation (Jones Speech), 1922-31 (Box 62, Folder 478)
  - Miscellaneous, 1931.Includes miscellaneous notes of Senator Jones
  - NOPQ, 1931 (Box 62, Folder 479)
  - Pest Control (Box 62, Folder 480)
  - Poet Laureate of California, 1931.Dr. Henry Meade Bland
  - Senate Resolution of Respect, April, 1931,on death of the poet
  - Political Expenditures (bill 391), 1931
  - Probate Code Bill no. 18
  - Probation
  - Public Utilities, 1931.Midland Counties' Public Service Corporation, Statistics from the California Railroad Commission's Department of Finance
  - R, 1931 (Box 62, Folder 481)
  - Railroads, 1931
  - Reapportionment (Bills SB 700, AB 1401) proposed Congressional District on basis of 1930 census.
  - Retail License Tax, 1931
  - S (Box 62, Folder 482)
  - Standardization, Fruit (Bill 446) (Box 62, Folder 483)
  - School Budgets
  - School Code, Amendments
  - School Elections, 1931
  - TUV, 1931 (Box 63, Folder 484)
  - Taxation and State Revenue (Box 63, Folder 485)
  - Report of Joint Legislative Committee on T axation, 48th Session, 1931
  - Taxation, 1923-31
  - Taxation and Cost of Government
  - Teachers' Pension, 1931 (Box 63, Folder 486)
  - Teachers' Pension. Santa Clara County (Box 63, Folder 487)
  - Teachers' Tenure (Box 63, Folder 488)
  - WXYZ, 1931
- INTERSESSION, 1932.After-Session Correspondence, 1931-32.Filed by name of Correspondent or by Subject Matter, when matter is evident
  - A-C (Box 64, Folder 489)
  - D-I (Box 64, Folder 490)
  - J-M (Box 64, Folder 491)
  - N-R (Box 64, Folder 492)
  - S-Z (Box 64, Folder 493)
- 1932CORRESPONDENCE AND REFERENCE MATERIALS, filed by Subject Matter
  - A-G (Box 65, Folder 494)
  - H-S (Box 65, Folder 495)
  - Misc. (Box 65, Folder 496)
  - T-Z (Box 65, Folder 497)
- 1933LEGISLATIVE SESSION. Legislative Correspondence, filed by name of Correspondent.
  - A-C (Box 65, Folder 498)
  - D-H (Box 65, Folder 499)
  - I-L (Box 66, Folder 500)
  - M (Box 66, Folder 501)
  - N-S (Box 66, Folder 502)
  - T-Z (Box 66, Folder 503)
- 1933LEGISLATIVE SESSION. Legislative Correspondence, filed by Subject Matter.
  - A, Legislative Correspondence: SM, 1933 (Box 66, Folder 504)
  - Adoption, 1933
  - Agriculture (Box 66, Folder 505)
  - Applicants-Sale tax, Liquor Control, etc.
  - Appreciation, letters of to Senator Jones
  - B, Legislative Correspondence, SM, 1933 (Box 66, Folder 506)
  - Banks
  - Barber Law (Box 67, Folder 507)
  - Beer
  - Bills of H.C. Jones (Box 67, Folder 508)
  - Bills, copies of, Legislature, 1933 (Box 67, Folder 509)
  - Bills, cont'd (Box 67, Folder 510)
  - Bills introduced in 1933Legislative Session, cont'd. (Box 67, Folder 511)
  - Bills, Correspondence in re: (Box 67, Folder 512)
  - Budget, State of California (Box 67, Folder 513)
  - Budget, State of California (Box 68, Folder 514)
  - Budget, Motor Vehicle Department (Box 68, Folder 515)
  - Building and Loan. Correspondence
  - Building and Loan. Bills, Amendments, Clippings, etc. (Box 68, Folder 516)
  - Bureau of Commerce
  - C, 1933 (Box 68, Folder 517)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 68, Folder 518)
  - Catholic Church
  - Cemeteries
  - Chain Stores (SB 72, AB 212, 1603, 888) (Box 69, Folder 519)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Bills: 250, 468, 543, 388, 389, 400) (Box 69, Folder 520)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1933-34
  - Chiropractors. Civil Service., Clippings (Box 69, Folder 521)
  - Clippings, Newspaper. Miscellaneous. unable to be identified according to Subject Matter.
  - Collection Agencies
  - Consolidation: Mergers (Box 69, Folder 522)
  - (Senate) C onstitutional Amendment no. 30. in re: financing of State Government, taxation of Real Property. (Box 69, Folder 523)
  - Cooperative Stores on Teachers' College Campus. (SB 757, AB 46, 336)
  - County Government (Box 69, Folder 524)
  - County Water Districts
  - County Budget
  - County Charter. Correspondence and Clippings
  - D, Legislative Correspondence, SM, 1933 (Box 69, Folder 525)
  - Deaf. Adult Lip reading, exemption from tuition classes.
    (see: SB 124, SB 2, in re: abolition of evening classes; AB 489, 480, in re: requirement of a tuition fee for evening schools.
  - E (Box 70, Folder 526)
  - Economic System
  - F (Box 70, Folder 527)
  - Fair Trade
  - Farm, Farm Bureau Federation
  - Federal Legislation and Federal Public Works
  - Filipino (Box 70, Folder 528)
  - Finance
  - Fish and Game
  - Flowers, State
  - G (Box 70, Folder 529)
  - Gambling, Horse Racing
  - Gas Tax, including material from: 1931, 32, 33, 34, 35.Correspondence and clippings. (Box 70, Folder 530)
  - H (Box 71, Folder 531)
  - Haynes Foundation. John Randolph and Dora Haynes. Declaration of Trust, Will, etc. (Box 71, Folder 532)
  - Highway Patrol (Box 71, Folder 533)
  - Historical Association
  - Holding Companies
  - Holidays
  - Humane Pound (SB 674). Folder no. 1 (Box 71, Folder 534)
  - Humane Pound. Folder no. 2 (Box 71, Folder 535)
  - I (Box 71, Folder 536)
  - Income Tax. Bills, Amendments, etc. (Box 72, Folder 537)
  - Initiative, League to Protect the, 1932-33 (Box 72, Folder 538)
  - Haynes, John R. - proceedings in support of the Initiative. Jones' argument for support of the Initiative. 10/24/32.
  - Initiative and Referendum. Folder no. 1. Special Election June 27, 1933. (Box 72, Folder 539)
  - Initiative and Referendum. Folder no. 2. Special Election June 27, 1933. (Box 72, Folder 540)
  - Initiative and Referendum. Folder no. 3 (Box 72, Folder 541)
  - Installment Taxes (Box 72, Folder 542)
  - (Senate) I nvestivating Committee. Investigation of Rolph Administration. Folder no. 1 (Box 72, Folder 543)
  - Investigating Committee. Rolph Administration. Folder no. 2 (Box 73, Folder 544)
  - Investigating Committee. Rolph Administration. Folder no. 3 (Box 73, Folder 545)
  - J (Box 73, Folder 546)
  - Judges, Justices
  - KL (Box 73, Folder 547)
  - Labor (Box 73, Folder 548)
  - Labor Commissioner. Correspondence, February-April, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 549)
  - Legislative Session, 1933
  - Miscellaneous Notes of Senator Jones, Newspaper Clippings on current Legislation.
  - M (Box 74, Folder 550)
  - Market Divisions. State Division of Markets under Department of Agriculture.
  - Married Women, occupational status of (Box 74, Folder 551)
  - Matton Act Moratorium
  - Mines. Question of discontinuing the Geological Survey Branch of the Division of Mines; for State Economy purposes
  - Moratoriums (see: Emergency Mortgages and Trust Deed Moratorium) (Box 74, Folder 552)
  - Motor Vehicles
  - Motor Vehicle Code
  - N (Box 74, Folder 553)
  - Narcotics Hospital
  - Nautical School
  - D (Box 74, Folder 554)
  - Old Age Pension
  - Office: miscellaneous correspondence, 1933 (Box 74, Folder 555)
  - P (Box 74, Folder 556)
  - Parks (Box 75, Folder 557)
  - Poet Laureate of California
  - Port San Jose
  - Primary Elections Law
  - Prohibition. Question of repeal of the 18th Amendment (Box 75, Folder 558)
  - Public Ownership
  - Public Health
  - Public Works, Department of. Employment
  - Public Utilities (Box 75, Folder 559)
  - Power Companies
  - Public Utilities and Transportation Companies' statistics filed with the California State Railroad Commission
  - R (Box 75, Folder 560)
  - Resolutions, Legislative
  - Requests for Notice
  - Research: Education Department (SB 117) in re: abolition of Division of Research and Statistics of State Department of Education (Box 75, Folder 561)
  - Retirement. Bill providing for the withdrawal of State participation in the Teachers' Retirement Fund
  - Riley Tax Bill (Box 76, Folder 562)
  - Roads and Highways (Box 76, Folder 563)
  - Road Signs
  - Road Tax
  - Rolph, Governor James, Jr. Question of Recall. (see: Senate Investigating Committee, 1933 (Box 76, Folder 564)
  - Rural Supervisor
  - S (Box 76, Folder 565)
  - Sales Tax. Bills, articles, clippings, amendments, etc. (Box 76, Folder 566)
  - San Francisco News. Clippings on Water Tax, Repeal of Prohibition, etc.
  - San Jose. City Charter and Miscellaneous data (Box 76, Folder 567)
  - Social Welfare
  - State Lands: Highways (SB 568, Senate Concurrent Resolution no. 17)
  - Syndicalism, Criminal
  - T (Box 77, Folder 568)
  - Taxation (Box 77, Folder 569)
  - Telephone calls to Senator Jones, 1933:miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 570)
  - Trucks
  - Trust Deeds (390, 391, 480) (Box 77, Folder 571)
  - Tuberculosis. in re: the lowering of State subsidy for TB patients, economy measure.
  - U (Box 77, Folder 572)
  - Unemployment, 1933
  - University, State. in re: proposed cut in University of California Budget.
  - Unseen Influences in the Molding of Political and Legislative Action. H.C. Jones, Speech before the Social Science Association of Southern California, luncheon meeting. Also folder contains letter from Franklin Hichborn with enclosures of speeches of US Assemblymen and Senators on: Finance, Foreign Debts, Banks, etc.
  - Utilities, Taxation of (SB 2, AB 307 in re: adjustment of utility tax rates) see: folder on Public Utilities and on Taxation, 1933. (Box 78, Folder 573)
  - V (Box 78, Folder 574)
  - Vandegrift. See: Senate Investigating Committee. Investigation of Rolph Administration
  - Veterans, Department
    Exemptions. Senate Finance Committee in re: State support of Education for relatives of deceased or disabled veterans
  - W (Box 78, Folder 575)
  - Water Plan, State. Central Valley Water Project.
  - Folder No. 1: Kennet Dam (Box 78, Folder 576)
    - Assembly Constitutional Amendment no. 18
    - SB 1201
    - Orange County Water District
  - Water Plan. Folder no. 2: Bills, Amendments, etc. (Box 78, Folder 577)
  - Water Plan. Folder no. 3: September 27, 1933,Application to Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works, Washington, D.C., for approval of Central Valley Water Project for California and for grant and loan for its construction under the provisions of the National Industrial Recovery Act of 1933. (Box 78, Folder 578)
  - Water Plan. Folder no. 4. Clippings, Bills, Amendments, etc. (Box 79, Folder 579)
  - Water Plan. Folder no. 5. Central Valley Water Project (Box 79, Folder 580)
  - Water Conservation and Water Districts (SB 567) (Box 79, Folder 581)
- INTERSESSION 1934.Filed by name of Correspondent and by Subject Matter, when latter is evident.
  - A (Box 79, Folder 582)
  - B (Box 79, Folder 583)
  - CD (Box 80, Folder 584)
  - Civil Service. Correspondence, 1933-34,including material from 1933-37 (Box 80, Folder 585)
  - EFG (Box 80, Folder 586)
  - HIJ (Box 80, Folder 587)
  - KIM (Box 80, Folder 588)
  - NOPQ (Box 80, Folder 589)
  - RS (Box 80, Folder 590)
  - TZ (Box 81, Folder 591)
- EDUCATION
  - Education: Adult Education. Folder no. 1 (Box 81, Folder 592)
  - H.C. Jones, Chairman of the Senate Education Committee, 1933
  - Education: Adult Education. Folder no. 2 (Box 81, Folder 593)
  - Education: Adult Education. Folder no. 3 (Box 81, Folder 594)
  - Education: Adult Education. Folder no. 4 (Box 81, Folder 595)
  - Education: Adult Education. Folder no. 5 (Box 82, Folder 596)
  - Education: Adult Education. Folder no. 6 (Box 82, Folder 597)
  - Education: Bills affecting Education, passed by Legislature, 1933;action taken on bills by Governor
  - Education: Senate Education Committee, Folder no. 1 (Box 82, Folder 598)
  - Education: Senate Education Committee, Folder no. 2 (Box 82, Folder 599)
  - Education: Clippings, Jones' Speeches, etc. (Box 82, Folder 600)
  - Education: Kindergartens. Folder no. 1: Petitions and Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 601)
  - Education: Kindergartens. Folder no. 2: Petitions and Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 602)
  - Education: Kindergartens. Folder no. 3 (Box 83, Folder 603)
  - Education: Kindergartens. Folder no. 4 (Box 83, Folder 604)
  - Education: Kindergartens. Folder no. 5 (Box 84, Folder 605)
  - Education: Kindergartens. Folder no. 6 (Box 84, Folder 606)
  - Education Physical Education (see: SB 432, 448, 515) (Box 84, Folder 607)
  - Education: Private, non-profit Schools. in re: the repeal of property tax on Private Schools (Box 84, Folder 608)
  - Education: Public Schools. Senate Constitutional Amendments no. I and III. Folder no. 1: Correspondence to Jones, Jan. 1-12, 1933 (Box 84, Folder 609)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 2: Correspondence Jan. 12, 1933 (Box 85, Folder 610)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 3: Correspondence, Jan. 13, 1933 (Box 85, Folder 611)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 4: Correspondence, Jan. 13, 1933 (Box 85, Folder 612)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 5: Correspondence, Jan. 13, 1933 (Box 85, Folder 613)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 6: Correspondence, Jan. 14, 1933 (Box 85, Folder 614)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 7: Correspondence, Jan. 14, 1933 (Box 85, Folder 615)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 8: Correspondence, Januart 15 - April 1933 (Box 86, Folder 616)
  - Education: Public Schools, SCA I, III. Folder no. 9: Cards and Telegrams to Senator Jones, January 2-16, 1933 (Box 86, Folder 617)
  - Education: Salaries, Sabbatical Leaves (Box 86, Folder 618)
  - Education: San Jose State Teachers' College. Folder no. 1: Bill before Legislature to reduce appropriations for SJSTC (Box 86, Folder 619)
  - Education: San Jose State Teachers' College. Folder no. 2. (Box 86, Folder 620)
  - Education: School Budgets (see: Senate Education Committee material, and SB 213) in re: placement of school budgets under the control of county supervisors (Box 86, Folder 621)
  - Education: Schools, Consolidation of School Districts. (see: AB 897, SB 231) (Box 86, Folder 622)
  - Education: School District Tax (School Code Amendment, SB 85) (Box 86, Folder 623)
  - Education: Schools. Fees, fixed charges, etc. (Box 87, Folder 624)
  - Education: Schools: Printed material, speeches, reports etc. in re: Education (Box 87, Folder 625)
  - Education: The Spitball, publication on Education (Box 87, Folder 626)
  - Education: Teachers' College Budget (Box 87, Folder 627)
  - Education: Teachers' Tenure, Folder no. 1 (Box 87, Folder 628)
  - Teachers' Tenure, Folder no. 2 (Box 87, Folder 629)
  - 1934-54. 1933was Senator Jones' last year in Legislative Session, 1934his last year as member of the State Legislature. (Box 88)
  - ABCD 1934-39. (Box 88, Folder 630)
    Material filed alphabetically according to Subject Matter of Correspondence and/or Reference Material; and chronologically within this division. For example: All material beginning with A: for years 1934-40, is filed first under A folder, then arranged chronologically, year after year, within the folder.
  - Anderson, Dewey vs. Crist, Frank L. Political Campaign for Assemblyman, 30th District. Folder includes Anderson-Jones Correspondence for 1934-35. (Box 88, Folder 631)
  - Board of Equalization, 1934-37;Liquor Control. (Box 88, Folder 632)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1935-36 (Box 88, Folder 633)
  - Child Labor, 1934
  - County Government, 1934
  - Clippings, Newspaper. Miscellaneous: Liquor Control, Power Trusts, etc., 1934 (Box 88, Folder 634)
  - Consolidation-Mergers, 1927-34 (Box 88, Folder 635)
  - Constitutional Convention. 1934, Clippings
  - E through Z 1934-39.Material filed alphabetically by Subject Matter (E-Z) and chronologically (1934-39)within this division. (Box 88, Folder 636)
  - Education, 1934.Letters, Newspaper Clippings, Leaflets (Box 89, Folder 637)
  - Elections, 1936.Folder no. 1: National and State Officials. State: new Progressive State organization. Question of Senator Borah in Presidential Primaries. Support for his candidacy sought among California progressives. (Box 89, Folder 638)
  - State: Mrs. Glasson, campaign for Assembly, 30th District.
  - Elections, 1936.Folder no. 2. Campaign for Assembly, 30th District: Maude Glasson, supported by Senator Jones. (Box 89, Folder 639)
  - Elections, 1936.Folder no. 3. (Box 89, Folder 640)
  - Farm, Grange, 1934 (Box 89, Folder 641)
  - Hetch Hetchy, 1934.Water supply tunnel to San Francisco. San Francisco News, clippings.
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1934.Folder no. 1 (Box 89, Folder 642)
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1934.Folder no. 2 (Box 90, Folder 643)
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1938.Garrison Revenue Bond Act no. 3 (Box 90, Folder 644)
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1938 (Box 90, Folder 645)
  - Legislature-Legislative Problems, 1934-35 (Box 90, Folder 646)
  - Legislation, 1935.San Jose and San Francisco Newspapers-clippings on current legislation, 1935Session. (Box 90, Folder 647)
  - Legislature, 1935.Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 648)
  - Political Campaign, 1934.County and State Offices. Correspondence and Clippings. (Box 90, Folder 649)
  - Taxation 1934-35 (Box 91, Folder 650)
  - Teachers. California Teachers' Association, 1934
  - Thompson, Carl. 1939(photograph addressed to Franklin Hichborn)
  - 1940-54:Miscellaneous Materials, no. 1 (Box 91, Folder 651)
  - 1940-54:Miscellaneous Materials, no. 2 (Box 91, Folder 652)
  - Immigration and Housing, 1941.Material from the Division of Immigration and Housing, State of California, Department of Industrial Relations. (Box 91, Folder 653)
- POLITICAL CAMPAIGN: GOVERNORSHIP, 1933-34.Herbert C. Jones campaigned for the nomination as Republican candidate for Governor, 1933-34.These folders contain Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Campaign Publicity, Speeches, and Jones' Notes - pertinent to the Campaign. Also, there are folders on Other Candidates for Governorship and Candidates for Other State Offices. 1933-34.
  - Alameda County (Box 91, Folder 654)
  - Announcement of Candidacy, H. C. Jones
  - Bartlett, Louis: Correspondence
  - Briggs, C.R. Correspondence: December 1933 - December 1934
    Briggs-Legislative Representative of A.T.O.L.A., Affiliated Teachers Organizations of Los Angeles. Correspondence in re: the Organization and its relationship to Jones' Candidacy and in re: Jones' progress in Southern California and elsewhere.
  - Cameron, W. H.
  - Central Valley Water Project
  - Clippings on H.C. Jones' Campaign (Box 92, Folder 655)
  - Correspondence, General in re: Campaign: Folder no. 1 (Box 92, Folder 656)
  - Correspondence, General in re: Campaign: Folder no. 2 (Box 92, Folder 657)
  - Chamber of Commerce, California State Creel, George (Box 92, Folder 658)
  - Colored People
  - Eberhard, Ray C. (Box 92, Folder 659)
  - Education: clippings
  - Ellis, W.R.
  - Givens, Willard E. (Box 93, Folder 660)
  - Glasson, Maude C.
  - Grange, Farmers (Box 93, Folder 661)
  - Haight, Raymond (Box 93, Folder 662)
  - Haynes, John Randolph
  - Hichborn, Franklin. Correspondence: September 1933 through October 1934.Folder no. 1: September 1933 - January 1934. (Box 93, Folder 663)
    Discussion of Candidates for Governor, of Jones' Campaign, his withdrawal from candidacy, The Progressive Cause in the State, etc.
  - Hichborn, Franklin. Correspondence. Folder no. 2: January 1934 - October 1934. (Box 93, Folder 664)
    Note on Hichborn Correspondence: Most of Hichborn's correspondence with Senator Jones in re: political campaign of 1933-34 is filed under Hichborn; however for several other letters from Hichborn see other folders in the Political Campaign: Governorship group. Certain letters from Hichborn which refer to another candidate, for instance, Maude Glasson, are filed in the Glasson folder.
  - Johnson, Charles G. (Box 93, Folder 665)
  - Lists (Box 93, Folder 666)
  - Labor (Box 93, Folder 667)
  - Legislative Record: Herbert C. Jones
  - Merriam, Frank (Box 94, Folder 668)
  - New Guard, The. A non-partisan organization of young, progressive voters (Box 94, Folder 669)
  - Newspapers
  - Northern California Campaign, H. C. Jones. Correspondence: September 1933 - January 1934.Folder no. 1 (Box 94, Folder 670)
  - Northern California Campaign, H.C. Jones. Correspondence: February - June 1934.Folder no. 2 (Box 94, Folder 671)
  - Other Candidates-State: Correspondence, Publicity, Clippings. (Box 94, Folder 672)
  - Other Candidates-County. Especially Sheriff of Santa Clara County. Folder includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, publicity for one candidate by F. Hichborn. (Box 95, Folder 673)
  - Jones, H.C. Platform and Policies. Clippings, correspondence, etc. (Box 95, Folder 674)
  - Political Straws, publication (Box 95, Folder 675)
  - Progressive Commonwealth Party
  - Publicity, Speeches, etc.-Jones (Box 95, Folder 676)
  - Public Ownership, Jones' position in re. (Box 95, Folder 677)
  - Quinn, John R.
  - Schools, Folder no. 1 (Box 95, Folder 678)
  - Schools, Folder no. 2 (Box 96, Folder 679)
  - Schools, lists of: Governorship 1933-34 (Box 96, Folder 680)
  - Seavy, Clyde L.
  - Sierra Educational News. Education publication. Jones' speech included.
  - Sinclair, Upton's candidacy for Governor. Clippings, Publicity, Articles by Hichborn and others. (Box 96, Folder 681)
  - Sonoma County (Box 96, Folder 682)
  - Social Welfare
  - Stanislaus County
  - Southern California Campaign. Folder no. 1: Correspondence, talks, etc., September 1933 - January 1934. (Box 96, Folder 683)
  - Southern California Campaign. Folder no. 2: Correspondence, etc., February, 1934 - May 1934. (Box 96, Folder 684)
  - Spreckles, Rudolph. Correspondence with Jones. (Box 96, Folder 685)
  - Taxation (Box 97, Folder 686)
  - Tenure
  - Utilities
  - Young, C.C.
  - Young voters
  - 1914Political Campaign No. 1 (Box 97, Folder 687)
  - 1914Political Campaign No. 2 (Box 97, Folder 688)
  - 1914Political Campaign No. 3 (Box 97, Folder 689)
  - 1914Political Campaign No. 4 (Box 97, Folder 690)
  - Herbert C. Jones: Biographical Information. (Box 97, Folder 691)
    Most of the materials in this folder are letters, magazine clippings, and publicity sheets that are duplicates of materials filed in the Correspondence and Reference folders for various years.
- Addendum
  The following papers were brought to Stanford by Herbert C. Jones after the arrangement of the above 1057 folders was completed. In sending his papers to Stanford this material was inadvertently overlooked.
  - Adult Education, 1926-30. (Box 98, Folder 692)
  - Cement Trust, 1929. (Box 98, Folder 693)
  - Clippings (about various Legislatures and Jones' participation). (Box 98, Folder 694)
  - Colorado River. Special Session, 1926.All-American Canal. (Box 98, Folder 695)